'Cause if she ever found out,
it would hurt her feelings.
(Bernadette:)Emily's feelings?
(Raj:)Yes, Emily.
Nice!
Yay!
Good job!
(Leonard:)Whatever.
Where's Sheldon?
(Amy:)Date night.
Mmm, that can't be
much fun for Amy.
(Leonard:)You know, at work today,
he tried his first Red Bull.
(Bernadette:)What happened?
(Leonard:)He chased a squirrel
(Leonard:)around the quad
for a while and...
(Leonard:)...then threw up in my car.
(Bernadette:)Don't you think you should
make him stop all this?
(Howard:)I don't know-- he's not
really hurting anybody.
(Leonard:)You didn't have to scoop vomit
out of your glove compartment.
(Sheldon:)He is getting
a lot of work done.
(Sheldon:)He had a pretty interesting
take on proton decay.
(Raj:)Wow, if he cracks that,
it's a game changer, guys.
(Raj:)It'll completely redefine
our understanding
(Raj:)of the physical universe.
(Howard:)Hmm, it would.
(Howard:)Okay, back to
"Emily or Cinnamon?"
"How can such a little girl
eat such a big steak?"